SEBASTIEN ZASADA

<u>LinkedIn | GitHub | Portfolio | References | sezasada@icloud.com</u>

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Driven professional with a broad technical skill set. Excellent communicator experienced in interpreting and implementing visions to meet the needs of the business. Known for the ability to efficiently manage multiple pressing projects simultaneously, consistently meeting deadlines and exceeding expectations. Excels in environments that constantly present new challenges.

Skills include:

HTML / CSS / React / Next / Redux / TypeScript / JavaScript / GraphQL / PostgreSQL / Amazon Web Services / Testing & Debugging / Project Management

EXPERIENCE

LandTrust - The Recreational Access Network

Software Engineer I - Remote

June 2023 - Present

- Developed a premium subscription service featuring a dynamic social feed with automated property updates, landowner-generated posts, custom notifications, a checkout page, a sales page, and more. This feature became one of the most widely used components of the application, driving significant revenue growth.
- Developed a new homepage with sections that display packages based on the users' geolocation, recently viewed packages using local storage, and the latest property updates posted by landowners.
- Created a system to effectively manage and decrease the frequency of incoming bugs, significantly reducing technical debt and clearing a backlog of hundreds of bugs and feature improvements.
- Managed our technical infrastructure by monitoring service costs and enforcing best practices to ensure optimal application performance and efficiency.
- Owned projects from inception to deployment, overseeing shaping, technical validation, development, and final release.

ByteSpeed

Focus Group Coordinator - Moorhead, MN

August 2019 - February 2020

- Led a 20-person focus group, including professors and teachers, to provide foundational training in virtual reality programs.
- Managed resources and collected feedback to drive the development of virtual reality solutions customized for our clients.
- Delivered clear, well-organized feedback reports to various VR companies, offering valuable, actionable insights.

EDUCATION

Emerging Digital Academy

November 2022 - May 2023

- Developed a secure application to track earnings reports of 2,500 companies, displaying real-time price changes and up-to-date news reports using third-party APIs.
- Presented my application to an audience of over 30 people, providing a detailed walkthrough of its features, technical implementation, and real-world applications for financial analysis.
- Developed a task management system for a nonprofit organization, which drastically increased efficiency, workflow, and organization for their business.

North Dakota State University - *Undergraduate Finance* **University of St. Thomas** - *Undergraduate Finance*